[Music]
[Applause]
for the first time in india insurance
alerts is recognizing three india's best
health insurance plans
the winners will be selected by our jury
members they are
mr vineet ogawa head strategy sales and
products star union daichi life
insurance company and mr ashish walia
chief marketing officer india first life
insurance company
hi i am vinit agarwal head sales
strategy and product development star
union daichi life insurance company
limited
i am happy
to be associated with free india's best
health insurance plan as jury remember
organized by insurance alerts
winning plans will be promoted at
national television channel on sunday
january 9 2022
the awards ceremony will be held in
mumbai on thursday december 23 2021
the winning plans will be also promoted
in all our social media platforms and
our own platforms reaching over 1.2
lakhs insurance agents twice daily
so what are you waiting for nominate
your health insurance plans today
insurance alerts is india's largest and
asia's second largest exclusive
insurance news platform reaching over
1.5 lakh insurance professionals in over
20 countries twice daily
insurance alerts broadcast world's only
exclusive insurance content youtube
channel with over 60 videos on insurance
we are connected to over 21 k on
linkedin
nomination closes on friday third
december 2021 so hurry
for more details call us on plus
917-977-33908 or write to us on events
at insurance alerts.com